const questions = [{
    numero: 1,
    question: "Which region are the Knights of Favonius located?",
    answer: ["Khaenriah", "Mondstadt", "Inazuma"],
    rightAnswer: "Mondstadt",
  },
  {
    numero: 2,
    question: "Who are the four beginner characters that you start the game with?",
    answer: ["Venti, Zhongli, Ei, Nahida", "Albedo, Sucrose, Traveler, Bennett", "Traveler, Lisa, Amber, Kaeya"],
    rightAnswer: "Traveler, Lisa, Amber, Kaeya",
  },
  {
    numero: 3,
    question: "What is the name of the pitstop between Mondstadt and Liyue?",
    answer: ["Dihua Marsh", "Wangshu Inn", "Dragonspine"],
    rightAnswer: "Wangshu Inn",
  },
  {
    numero: 4,
    question: "What is the name of your Silver haired flying companion",
    answer: ["Paimon", "Spymon", "Byemon"],
    rightAnswer: "Paimon",
  },
  {
    numero: 5,
    question: "What element does the traveler acquire first in Teyvat?",
    answer: ["Anemo", "Geo", "Electro"],
    rightAnswer: "Anemo",
  },
  {
    numero: 6,
    question: "Which island of Inazuma is known for its Aztec-like story theme?",
    answer: ["Yashiori Island", "Watatsumi Island", "Tsurumi Island"],
    rightAnswer: "Tsurumi Island",
  },
  {
    numero: 7,
    question: "What are the demon names of the currently confirmed archons?",
    answer: ["Santa, Rudolf, Satan, George, Frank, Jim", "Barbatos, Morax, Beelzebuul, Buer, Focalors, Murata", "Bermuda, Borax, Baal, Beer, Folklore, Murakami"],
    rightAnswer: "Barbatos, Morax, Beelzebuul, Buer, Focalors, Murata",
  },
  {
    numero: 8,
    question: "How many Fatui Harbingers were there originally (We don't talk about Signora)?",
    answer: ["11", "9", "6"],
    rightAnswer: "11",
  },
  {
    numero: 9,
    question: "Who was it who originally sealed away the traveler and their twin?",
    answer: ["Kiana Kaslana", "The Sustainer of Heavenly Principles", "The Principality of Celestia"],
    rightAnswer: "The Sustainer of Heavenly Principles",
  },
  {
    numero: 10,
    question: "What are the virtues of the currently encountered archons of Teyvat (as of 3.0)?",
    answer: ["Love, Justice, Wisdom, War", "Justice, Transience, Freedom, War", "Freedom, Contracts, Eternity, Wisdom"],
    rightAnswer: "Freedom, Contracts, Eternity, Wisdom",
  },
  {
    numero: 11,
    question: "The Tianquan of the Liyue Qixing is?",
    answer: ["Keqing", "Qiqi", "Ningguang"],
    rightAnswer: "Ningguang",
  },
  {
    numero: 12,
    question: "What is the name of the cell in which Nahida was imprisoned?",
    answer: ["Sanctuary of Samsara", "Sanctuary of Suresthana", "Sanctuary of Shamshir"],
    rightAnswer: "Sanctuary of Suresthana",
  },
  {
    numero: 13,
    question: "Who is the First descender?",
    answer: ["Celstia", "Phanes", "Traveler"],
    rightAnswer: "Phanes",
  },
  {
    numero: 14,
    question: "What is the name of the princess of Sal Vindagnyr's protector?",
    answer: ["Irminsul", "Imunlaukr", "Imminent"],
    rightAnswer: "Imunlaukr",
  },
  {
    numero: 15,
    question: "Who was responsible for the sacrifice of King Deshret?",
    answer: ["Greater Lord Rukkhedevata", "Himself", "Lesser Lord Kusanali"],
    rightAnswer: "Himself",
  },
  {
    numero: 16,
    question: "Before the First Who Came, who, or what, were the original inhabitants of Teyvat?",
    answer: ["Celestia", "Orobashi", "Dragonheirs of the Depths"],
    rightAnswer: "Dragonheirs of the Depths",
  },
  {
    numero: 17,
    question: "What is the name of Albedo's brother, also created by Rhinedottir?",
    answer: ["Durin", "Dvalin", "Daran"],
    rightAnswer: "Durin",
  },
  {
    numero: 18,
    question: "What is the name of the creator of the Dainichi Mikoshi?",
    answer: ["Aberaku", "Supada", "Daimon"],
    rightAnswer: "Aberaku",
  },
  {
    numero: 19,
    question: "The origin of the Black Serpent Knights is?",
    answer: ["The Chasm", "Enkanomiya", "Khaenriah"],
    rightAnswer: "Khaenriah",
  },
  {
    numero: 20,
    question: "What are the names of the Moon Sisters?",
    answer: ["Seelie, Hili, Canon", "Aria, Sonnet, Canon", "Aria, Seelie, Hili"],
    rightAnswer: "Aria, Sonnet, Canon",
  },
  {
    numero: 21,
    question: "The Guili Assembly of Liyue was ruled by which god?",
    answer: ["Zhongli", "Havria", "Guizhong"],
    rightAnswer: "Guizhong",
  },
  ];